<resources>

    <string name="app_name">TheActivityManager</string>

    <string name="text_0">Please wait when you clicked a button, it will automatically generates activities and launch them by itself.</string>
    <string name="text_1">Launch 3 more activities, and turn back to this landing activity.</string>
    <string name="text_2">Launch 3 more activities, one has different instance and finish that one.</string>
    <string name="text_3">Launch 3 more activities, one has different instance and finish the other activities until that one.</string>
    <string name="text_4">Launch an activity as a step and send extra from this activity to further one!</string>
    <string name="text_5">Launch 3 more activities, and quit from application.</string>

    <string name="type_none">If you are having this type, something went wrong!</string>
    <string name="type_to_landing">You will turn back to landing page when you click, and every activity between this and landing will be finished.</string>
    <string name="type_remove_instance">The different instance will be removed and finished when you go back!</string>
    <string name="type_to_instance">It will go back to different instance and remove others between this activity and that one.</string>
    <string name="type_step">When you click, it will start a new activity which has extra from previous one. \n\nConsider this activity as a middle step that you had to deal with something in this layer but you do not need it anymore. \n\nSo when you move it will self destroy (optional)</string>
    <string name="type_quit">On your click it will finish every one of activity has been created till now, and quit from application.</string>

    <string name="dialog_ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="dialog_remove_instance">Press back button until landing, and you will not see that instance on the way back!</string>
    <string name="dialog_step">This message comes from landing activity!</string>

    <string name="final_button_text">Show Me!</string>

</resources>
